knowurcollege.com 2012-11-16

# Privacy Policy for www.knowurcollege.com | KnowurCollege.com

**Privacy Policy for www.knowurcollege.com**

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at info@knowurcollege.com.

At www.knowurcollege.com, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by www.knowurcollege.com and how it is used.

**Log Files**  
Like many other Web sites, www.knowurcollege.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**  
www.knowurcollege.com does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

**DoubleClick DART Cookie**  
.:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on www.knowurcollege.com.  
.:: Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to www.knowurcollege.com and other sites on the Internet.  
.:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include ….  
Google Adsense

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on www.knowurcollege.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

www.KnowurCollege.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. www.knowurcollege.com’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

**Content   Policy**

  * Content on this website has been written with the reference of online material, news and different source of websites.  It is possible that the present information can be vary from our content as it has been written a long ago. In This case Please request us to change the content as per present scenario. Please email us at info@knowurcollege.com  

  * We reserved right to change the content, delete the content, delete the pages and information on this website any time.  

  * We believe the content presented here can not be %100 accurate as well correct. It could be vary from other source of information. 

**Image Policy**

  * Images we have shown here is contains ownership of their respected owner. We are not owning this images and used here for reference purpose only.
  * If You are contain ownership for Images and do want us to use it. kindly email us at info@knowurcollege.com to remove it.

**Commenting and inquiry form fill up Policy  
**

  * Make your contact details available to Knowurcollege.com partners, you may be contacted by Knowurcollege.com partners for education information through email, telephone and SMS, if you do not wish to be contacted, you may click on unsubscribe link on email.
  * Receive promotional mails/special offers from Knowurcollege.com or any of its partner websites

**Along with**

  * Knowurcollege.com is created for information purpose only . The information we have presented here is a best with our knowledge and collected from web.  The information might be wrong or out dated  and Visitor will only responsible for his/her own decision.
  * we are not providing any services.

Rating: 5.0/ **10** (1 vote cast)
